<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tech Gadgets</string>
    <string name="rice">Zojirushi Rice Cooker</string>
    <string name="mixer">KitchenAid Stand Mixer</string>
    <string name="console">XBox 360 Game Console</string>
    <string name="dance">DDR Foam Dancepad</string>
    <string name="VR">Valve Index VR Headset</string>

    <string name="riceinfo">A rice cooker is an automated kitchen appliance designed to boil or steam rice.
        The Zojirushi brand cooker has several settings to cook many different kinds of rice, porridge, and mixed rice.
    </string>
    <string name="mixinfo">Stand Mixers are kitchen appliances that are used primarily for mixing types of dough for baking, but can be used for any type of mixing tasks.
        They come with several attachments, including a dough hook, a whisk, and a paddle.
        Additional front attachments increase the versatility of the Kitchen Aid brand by enabling the mixer to do things mixers traditionally don\'t do.
    </string>
    <string name="consoleinfo">The XBox brand is a long standing brand of game consoles, featuring popular titles, and exclusives such as the Forza racing series.
        Developed by Microsoft, the system was designed to run on the Windows Operating System, allowing developers to leverage their computers to make games more efficiently
    </string>
    <string name="danceinfo">Dance Dance Revolution is a series of games that gained popularity in the early 2000s, through the 2010s.
        Originally DDR was a series of arcade games that featured music, animations, and an interactive screen with arrows.
        The cabinets featured a large metal platform to control the game through using the feet.
        The game was subsequently ported to various consoles due to its popularity, however, its design necessitated the creation of a dance pad style game controller.
        The foam version is vastly superior to the once widely available cheap folding plastic versions.
    </string>
    <string name="VRinfo">The Index is a virtual reality headset created by the Valve Corporation. Although, it is not the first of its kind, it was the top of the line when it launched.
        This version of the headset features two handheld controllers, and two base stations that triangulate the position of the player.
        The headset features 6 sensors for positioning, and high resolution OLED displays. However, its main flaw is the fact it is connected to the computer via a cord, that the user can trip over.
        Future iterations of the headset are wireless. Although the VR market still commonly features drastic hardware changes, and proprietary equipment, it is a growing industry with a huge consumer footprint
    </string>
</resources>